Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of art Womens Committee records, circa 1960-2001 COR0008.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Women's Committee files, 1954-1993; Series 5
  - 1982 - Menu, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1982 - Complementary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1982 - Entertainment, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1982 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1982 - Parties for Ball, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1982 - Committee / Minutes, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1982 - Correspondance, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1983 - Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1983 - Committee / Minutes, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1983 - Complimentary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1983 - Correspondance, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1983 - Decorations, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1983 - Dinner, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1983 - Finances (Bills), Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1983 - Finances (Contrabutions), Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1983 - Invitation / Program, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1983 - Music, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1983 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1983 - Seating / Door List, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1984 - Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1984 - Beverages, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1984 - Committee / Minutes, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1984 - Correspondance, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1984 - Dinner, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 1983 - Finances (Contrabutions), Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1984 - Invitations / Programs, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1984 - Music, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1984 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1984 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1984 - Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1984 - Ball Committee, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1984 - Ball Committee Minutes, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1984 - Chairman's Ball Report, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1984 - Ball Favors, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1984 - Beverages, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 1984 - Corporate Underwriters/Sponsors/Benefactors, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - 1984 - Decorations, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 1984 - Dinner, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 1984 - Files, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 1984 - General Committee, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 1984 - Honorary Patrons, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 1984 - Invitations, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 1984 - Music, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 1984 - Program, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 1984 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - 1984 - Seating, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - 1984 - Thank You Letters, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1984 - VIP Reception, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 1984 - Volunteers, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1985 - Arrangement, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 1985 - Beverages, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 1985 - Brunch, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1985 - Brunch, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 1985 - Cocktail Party, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1985 - Committee / Minutes, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1985 - Correspondance, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1985 - Decorations, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - 1985 - Dinner, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 1985 - Finances (sponsors), Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - 1985 - Files, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - 1985 - Finances (taxes), Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - 1985 - Finances (treasury), Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - 1985 - Guest List / Seating, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - 1985 - Music, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - 1985 - Public Program / Invitation, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - 1985 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - 1985 - Tea, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - 1985 - Thank Yous, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - 1985 - Underwriting, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - 1986 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1986 Ball Committee, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1986 Beverages, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1986 Corporate Underwriters/Sponsers/Benefactors, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1986 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1986 Dinner, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1986 Favors, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1986 Files, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1986 General Committee, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1986 General Committee Reception, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1986 Honorary Patrons, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1986 Invitations, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1986 Printing of Invitation, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1986 Music, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1986 Programs, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1986 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1986 Seating, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1986 Tax Deductions, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 1986 Thank You Letters, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1986 Treasurer, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1986 VIP Receptions, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1986 Volunteers, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1987 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1987 Ball Committee, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1987 Ball Committee Minutes, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1987 Ball Favors, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1987 Chairman's Ball Report, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1987 Beverages, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1987 Corporate Underwriters/Sponsors/Benefactors Etc., Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1987 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 1987 Dinner, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1987 Files, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1987 General Committee, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Honorary Patrons, 1986; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1987 Invitation, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1987 Music, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1987 Program, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1987 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1987 Seating, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1987 Thank You Letters, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1987 Treasurer, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1987 VIP Reception, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1987 Volunteers, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 1988 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1988 Ball Committee, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1988 Ball Committee Minutes, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 1988 Ball Favors (empty), Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 1988 Beverages (empty), Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 1988 Chairman's Ball Report (empty), Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - 1988 Corporate Underwriters/Sponsors/Benefactors, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - 1988 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - 1988 Dinner, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 1988 Files, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 1988 General Committee, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 1988 Honorary Patrons (empty), Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - 1988 Invitation, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 1988 Music, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - 1988 Program, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - 1988 Thank You Letters, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - 1988 Treasurer (empty), Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - 1988 VIP Reception, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - 1988 Volunteers, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 1988 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 1988 Seating, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 1989 Ball Menu, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Board of Trustees Letter, 1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fowler Grant, 1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Corporate Donors List from CGA, 1982-1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Special Letters AT, 1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Carolyn Amiot's A-E Master List, 1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Corporate Replies Xerox Response Cards, 1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Other Corporate Letters Ford, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Special, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Merrill Lynch, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Big Hit Speical Letter Address List CBS, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Renew Benefactor or jumps to Lion's Circle, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - B3, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Ginny Boothe's Master File Aug 3 Mailing, 1988 August 3; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Me Letters A-E Types, 1989; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Sample Letters Underwriters, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Nordstrom Nina Me, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - AT, 1988; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Corcoran Ball 1989, Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 1989 - Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1989 - Ball Committee Minutes, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1989 - Ball Committee, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1989 - Beverages, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1989 - Chairman's Ball Report, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1989 - Corcoran Ball - ITT Corportation, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1989 - Corporate underwriters / sponsors / benefactors, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1989 - Decorations, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1989 - Dinner, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1989 - Favors, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1989 - Files, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1989 - General Committee, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1989 - Honorary Patrons, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1989 - Invitation, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1989 - Music, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1989 - Program, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1989 - Publicity, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1989 - Seating, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1989 - Thank You Letters, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1989 - Treasurer, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1989 - VIP Reception, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1989 - Volunteers, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1990 - Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1990 - Ball Committee, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1990 - Ball Committee Minutes, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1990 - Favors, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1990 - Beverages, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1990 - Chairman's Ball Report, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 1990 - Corporate Underwriters / Sponsors / Benefactors, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 1990 - Decorations, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - 1990 - Dinner, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - 1990 - Honorary Patrons, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 1990 - General Committee, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 1990 - Invitations, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 1990 - Music, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - 1990 - Program, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 1990 - Seating, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 1990 - Thank You Letters, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 1990 - Treasurer, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 1990 - Files, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 1990 - Volunteers, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - 1990 - VIP Reception, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Arrangements, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Addressing, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ball Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ball Committee Stationing, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ball Favors, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ball Logistics Meeting - Walk Through, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Ball Meeting French Embassy, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ball Meetings Minutes, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ball Walk - Through Meeting, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Bands, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Beverages, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Chairmans Report, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Complimentary Tickets, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Corporate - underwriters, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Corporate - Ball Tickets, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Corporate Printing D. Daniels, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Decorations, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dinner, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Fact Sheet, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Flower Decorations, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Greeters, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - General Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Former Trustee Letter, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Complementary Tickets, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Corporate Supplies, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Letters, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Program 1991, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Invitation Lists, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - President Bush Letter, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Program - underwriter Page, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Press Kit, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Public Relations, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Nynex, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Tiffany Corporate Gift, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Thank You Letters - After Ball, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Treasurer, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Trustee Letter - Former, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Tiffany, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - VIP Reception, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Joyce, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Arrangements, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Arthur Andersonn - Co., Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Addressing, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Ball Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Ball Committee Minutes, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Ball Committee Stationary, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Corporate Responses, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Coorporate Letters, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Corporrate Solicitations, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - British Embassy, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - French Embassy Reception, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Generral Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Greeters, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Invitations, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Nynex - 1992, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Program, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Publicity, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Chairman's Report, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Trustees, 1992; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Corcoran Ball, Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer, 1992; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1992 Corcoran Ball, Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Ball Report 1993, Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Ball Addressing, Undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Corcoran Ball Arrangements, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran Ball Beverages, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Corcoran Ball Bills, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Ball Ball Committee, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Ball Ball Committee Meetings, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ball Weekend Invites, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran Ball Corporate Committee, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Corcoran Ball List, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Corcoran Ball Decorations, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Ball Dinner/Menu, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Corcoran Ball Favors/Corporate Gifts, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Corcoran Ball Files/Invitation List, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Corcoran Ball Invitation Printing, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Corcoran Ball General Committee, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Corcoran Ball Corporate Gift Delivery, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Corcoran Ball Orchestras, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Corcoran Ball Nynex, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Corcoran Ball Program, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Corcoran Ball Contribution Acknowledgement, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Corcoran Ball Honorary Patron, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Corcoran Ball Press/Publicity, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Corcoran Ball Printing, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Corcoran Ball Reservataions, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Corcoran Ball Seating, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Corcoran Ball Treasurer, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - RSVP, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Corcoran Ball VIP Reception, 1993; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Special Trips-Programs, 1978-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Membership Committee, 1980; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lectures, 1970-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Speakers for Women's Committee Meetings, 1982-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Membership, 1983-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Art School, 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Friends, 1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Friends, 1980-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Gallery Building, Trustees and Staff, 1982-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Budget Propsal, 1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, 1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1985; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Projects and Benefits, 1983-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Budget Director's Proposals, 1976-1982; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1983; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Women's Committee Executive Minutes, 1978-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - New Members Advisory, 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Acquisitions, Undated; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Special Projects Staircase, Undated; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Press, 1962-1984; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Trustee Handbook Binder (Mapplethorpe Press) (1 of 3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Trustee Handbook Binder (Mapplethorpe Press) (2 of 3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Trustee Handbook Binder (Mapplethorpe Press) (3 of 3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Corcoran Ball Publications, Undated; Series 5 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Minutes, meetings files, and reports, 1905-2001; 1957-2001; Series 6
  - Final Reports, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Treasurers - Budget, 1993-1998; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1997-1998; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - May 1999 Meeting, 1999 May; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - April 1999 Meeting, 1999 April; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - March 1999 Meeting, 1999 March; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - February 1999 Meeting, 1999 February; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - January 1999 Meeting, 1999 January; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - November 1998 Meeting, 1998 November; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - October 1998 Meeting, 1998 October; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - September 1998 Meeting, 1998 September; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - May 1998 June Exec. Meeting, 1998 May; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - April 1998 Meeting, 1998 April; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - March 1998 Meeting, 1998 March; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - February 1998 Meeting, 1998 February; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - January 1998 Meeting, 1998 January; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - November 1997 Meeting, 1997 November; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - October 1997 Meeting, 1997 October; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - September 1997 Meeting, 1997 September; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Art Acquisition, 1993-1999; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 1997 Summer Programs, Committee Assignments, Committee Dates, Night Day Deadlines, 1997 June; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Membership, 1998-1999; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Art School (empty), Circa 1950s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Ball 1998, 1905 June 20; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Ball 1997, 1905 June 19; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Ball 1999, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Business Professional Women of the Corcoran, 1905 June 20; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Education and Special Groups/Trips, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Letters to and from Women's Committee, 1997-1999; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Dudley Memorial Lecture, 1905 June 13; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Gallery Beautification, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Memorial Funds, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Museum Shop, 1998-1999; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - New Members Advisory, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Nominating Committee, 1905 June 20; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Program, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Project, 1905 June 20; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Upscale Tag Sale, 1905 June 21; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Salon Dore, 1905 June 20; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Corcoran Capital Planning, 1905 June 20; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Executive Committe, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Agendas, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Regular Minutes, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Regular Minutes, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Agendas, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - September 1996 Meeting, 1996 September; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - September 1995 Meeting, 1995 September; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - September 1996 Meeting, 1996 September; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - October 1995 Meeting, 1995 October; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - November 1996 Meeting, 1996 November; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - November 1995 Meeting, 1995 November; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - December 1996 Meeting, 1996 December; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Decemebr 1995 Meeting, 1995 December; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - January 1997 Meeting, 1997 January; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - January 1996 Meeting, 1996 January; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - February 1997 Meeting, 1997 February; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - February 1996 Meeting, 1996 February; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - March 1997 Meeting, 1997 March; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Executive Committe, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - March 1996 Meeting, 1996 March; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - April 1997 Meeting, 1997 April; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - April 1996 Meeting, 1996 April; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - May 1997 Meeting, 1997 May; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - May 1996 Meeting, 1996 May; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Art Acquisition, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Beautification, 1996 June; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Art Acquisitions, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Dudley, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - By-Laws, 1905 June 18; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Education Trips, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Membership/WC, 1905 June 18; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Museum Shop, 1905 June 19; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - VCAM, 1905 June 19; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Handbook, 1905 June 18; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Memorials, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Projects, 1905 June 19; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Upscale Tag Sale, 1905 June 19; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - French Room, 1905 June 17; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - A Review of Operations "The Corcoran", Circa 1950s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Tiny Jewel Box, 1905 June 18; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - News, 1981-1993; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Exhibition Schedule CGA, 1996-1998; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Mailing Labels WC/CGA, Circa 1950s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Jeannette/Leadership, Circa 1950s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Chairman Leader of WC, Circa 1950s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Dali Preview Ball, 1956 February 24; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund, 2000-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 2)